[
   {
    "product_id": 1,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Pidgeotto",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001001",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 2,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Pikachu",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001002",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 3,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Dragonite",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001003",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 4,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Vulpix",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001004",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/pokemon/vulpix-box-1.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 5,
    "licence_name": "Pokemon",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Charmander",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "PKM001005",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 6,
    "licence_name": "Star Wars",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Baby Yoda",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001001",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 7,
    "licence_name": "Star Wars",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Bobbafeth",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001002",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 8,
    "licence_name": "Star Wars",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Luke",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001003",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp"
  },

  {
    "product_id": 9,
    "licence_name": "Star Wars",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Trooper",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Star Wars",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "STW001004",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 10,
    "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Harry",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HPT001001",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 11,
    "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Hermione",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HPT001002",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 12,
    "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Luna",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HPT001003",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp"
  },
  {
    "product_id": 13,
    "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
    "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
    "product_name": "Snape",
    "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Harry Potter",
    "product_price": 1799.99,
    "dues": 10,
    "product_sku": "HPT001004",
    "img_front": "/assets/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp",
    "img_back": "/assets/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp"
  }

]

